

Pantelis Stathatos

Contact

Address:

Phone:

Skurou 25, Athens (+30) 6981114657

Email:

stathatos.pant@gmail.com

GitHub O

https://github.com/PantelisStathatos

Languages

English – C2

Greek – Native

Education

- Level 5 (EU) degree: Junior
 Software Engineer
 I.IEK ΑΛΦΑ
 Athens Greece
 9/2017- 6/2019
- Greek General High school
 Degree
 9/2014 6/2017

Personal Highlights

- Easy Learner
- Multitasking
- Adaptive
- Great people skills
- Communicative
- o Team Player
- Problem solver

Interests and Hobbies

- Amateur guitar player
- Music addict
- o Web design
- o Graphic design and Arts
- Cooking
- o Video games
- Movies and Books
- PC Building and Hardware

*I.IEK = Vocational Training Institutes

Summary

I am a **Junior Software Engineer**, Graduate* of I.IEK ΑΛΦΑ*, with an **overall three years** into my field and more than **one year** of work experience, looking to develop my skills in both back-end and front-end **software development**. A major part of my working experience based on Microsoft's **.NET** Framework, more specifically with **ASP.NET** Framework, and **CI/CD** practices on a JEE product. In the past year I have developed an interest in **Web Development**, and currently I am looking into advancing my knowledge and skills regarding web development.

Academic and **personal knowledge** includes: Java, C, C++, C#, vanilla JS, HTML, CSS and CSS frameworks, OOP practices and modern software lifecycles and maintenance.

Work Experience

.NET Junior Developer

@ Byte Computer A.B.E.E - 2/6/2020 - 4/1/2021

- Software developer at, various MVC structured, ASP.NET
 (Framework 4.8 and older) products, with responsibilities that would include bug
 fixing, code re-formatting or fixing versioning issues caused by badly
 formatted .aspx files. Through those products, some experience with MS SQL was
 gained.
- Took extended training in Microsoft's 365 Power Platform, which included development in Power Apps, combining and using Power Automate with other components and/or products, and using SharePoint's online capabilities alongside Power Apps and Power Automate.
- For each of the above, two Projects were created to demonstrate my knowledge and understanding of the given tasks I was to be assigned. Those include a <u>leave</u> <u>request</u> app based on the company's business needs, created as a Power Apps Canvas app, and a <u>Employee management</u> web app on ASP.NET Framework 4.8 using MVC structure.

Continuous Integration (CI) Engineer Internship @ UNIFY Greece – 2/1/2020 - 2/6/2020

- CI Engineer on a Scrum team, with responsibilities such as developing, monitoring, and supporting Continuous Integration (CI) pipelines, setting-up new test suites on a CI environment, and analyzing CI tests results.
- Learned and used Tools/Frameworks such Jenkins, Selenium, VMware,
 TestNG, Maven, Git, WLS and Groovy, while getting familiar with Agile Software
 Development and CI related subjects like testing methods on a big and scalable product (Product name: Circuit).

Back-end VB.NET developer - 1/9/2019 - 27/9/2019

Certifications

- o Basics of Cryptomining and cryptocurrency trading by KORELKO Educational Institute
- GPS and Telematic Applications by KORELKO Educational Institute
- o Game Design Basics by KORELKO Educational Institute
- o Safety on Web and Social Media by KORELKO Educational Institute
- Dark/Deep Web by KORELKO Educational Institute
- Secrets of Social Media Marketing by I.IEK ΑΛΦΑ Education Festival 2019
- o **GDPR Regulation** by I.IEK ΑΛΦΑ Education Festival 2019
- Artificial Inteligence by I.IEK ΑΛΦΑ Education Festival 2019
- Smart grids and challenges The Spear Project by I.IEK ΑΛΦΑ Education Festival 2019
 2nd Anuall conference orginized by Info Mobillity World